{
    "subject": "resource/Bye,_See_You_Monday",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_directed_by_Maurice_Dugowson",
    "human_readable": "Bye, See You Monday is about Films directed by Maurice Dugowson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9658984541893005,
            "question": "What is Maurice Dugowson known for directing besides 'Bye, See You Monday'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9397064447402954,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Bye, See You Monday'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.892696738243103,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Maurice Dugowson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7689872980117798,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Bye, See You Monday'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6379238963127136,
            "question": "Where was 'Bye, See You Monday' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5903047919273376,
            "question": "Are there any notable actors in 'Bye, See You Monday'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5837082862854004,
            "question": "What year was 'Bye, See You Monday' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4504333734512329,
            "question": "What themes does 'Bye, See You Monday' explore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4425387978553772,
            "question": "What is the overall critical reception of 'Bye, See You Monday'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43448343873023987,
            "question": "Has 'Bye, See You Monday' won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bye, See You Monday is about Films directed by Maurice Dugowson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1705_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall critical reception of 'Bye, See You Monday'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1705_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes does 'Bye, See You Monday' explore?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1705_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'Bye, See You Monday' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1705_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1705_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1705_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1705_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1705_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1705_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1705_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1705_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1705_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1705_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1705_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Bye, See You Monday is a film directed by Maurice Dugowson.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention that Maurice Dugowson directed the film \"Bye, See You Monday,\" and details about its plot and festival entries are provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}